<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>beepizza</title>
	<atom:link href="http://https://github.com/tee275/beepizza.github.io.git/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://https://github.com/tee275/beepizza.github.io.git</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 06:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0</generator>
	<item>
		<title>What Is On A Teriyaki Chicken Pizza ?</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/tee275/beepizza.github.io.git/2022/04/15/hello/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/tee275/beepizza.github.io.git/2022/04/15/hello/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[pizza]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 05:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Pizza]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/tee275/beepizza.github.io.git/?p=351</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This pizza in and of itself doesn’t take a ton [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>This pizza in and of itself doesn’t take a ton of time to make. But… if you are making all of the components from scratch (which I highly recommend!) it will take a little longer. The good thing is that much of it can be made in advance!</p>



<ul><li><strong>The Teriyaki</strong> – my homemade teriyaki chicken is perfect in this recipe. It’s more like a glaze because it is quite thick, which is what you’ll need for this recipe. It can be made even a few days in advance, plus you’ll have extra to use in other recipes, as well.</li><li><strong>The Pizza Dough</strong> – I have been making my homemade pizza dough almost weekly for years now. You could definitely use a store bought crust, but I have a feeling that if you tried my homemade dough, you’d be hooked, too! I will usually make the dough earlier in the morning for dinner that night, but really, you could make it a day ahead of time and put it in the refrigerator (be careful, though, as it will continue to rise, just not as fast) or you could freeze portions so that you just have to defrost your dough that day. Make sure and read through my post for all of the tips for making the pizza dough. I know it’s long, but it is all important information!</li><li><strong>The Chicken</strong> – All you really need to do is cut and cook the chicken, and this will just take a few minutes, especially since it’s not a lot of chicken. Technically you could do this ahead of time, as well, but it’s so quick that it’s really not necessary!</li><li><strong>The Pineapple</strong> – I have used both fresh and canned pineapple in this recipe before. While I definitely prefer the flavor of fresh, canned will work. You may need to cut the pieces smaller, though, so that you don’t have big chunks of pineapple on your pizza.</li><li><strong>The Rest</strong> – Cheese and cilantro are the last two ingredients you’ll need. I recommend freshly grated Mozzarella, as it will melt better. You don’t necessarily need fresh mozzarella, though – I just use the brick of cheese from the grocery store. Pre-grated cheese is coated to keep it from sticking together, and this makes it so that it doesn’t melt as well. For the cilantro – I know some people don’t like it, so you can leave it off. But I love the bit of freshness and flavor it brings.</li></ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/tee275/beepizza.github.io.git/2022/04/15/hello/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ingredients of Pepperoni Feast</title>
		<link>http://https://github.com/tee275/beepizza.github.io.git/2022/03/28/chao-moi-nguoi/</link>
					<comments>http://https://github.com/tee275/beepizza.github.io.git/2022/03/28/chao-moi-nguoi/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[pizza]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 08:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Pizza]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://https://github.com/tee275/beepizza.github.io.git/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Enriched bleached wheat flour (bleached flour, malted barley flour, niacin, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Enriched bleached wheat flour (bleached flour, malted barley flour, niacin, ferrous sulfate, thiamin mononitrate, riboflavin, folic acid), water, yeast, salt, sugar, soybean and/or cottonseed oil, whey, may contain 2% or less of enzymes and/or datem, vital wheat gluten, potassium sorbate (preservative), ascorbic acid, sodium stearoyl lactylate. cheese: Part skim mozzarella cheese (pasteurized milk, cheese cultures, salt, enzymes), modified food starch, whey protein concentrate, non- fat milk, sodium propionate (added as a preservative). sauce: Tomato paste, water, salt, spices, garlic powder, and citric acid. pepperoni: Pork, beef, salt, spices, water, dextrose, oleoresin of paprika, flavorings, lactic acid starter culture, sodium nitrite, bha, bht, citric acid.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://https://github.com/tee275/beepizza.github.io.git/2022/03/28/chao-moi-nguoi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
